Enoch Chejieh

Software Engineer

enoch@acumen.com.ng +2348115911976 https://www.linkedin.com/in/enoch-chejieh-a39652155

https://github.com/ECJ222 https://enochchejieh.netlify.app Lagos, Nigeria

SUMMARY

Enoch Chejieh is a software engineer with 1+ years of experience ranging from frontend to backend technologies.

Experienced Frontend developer (VueJs, NuxtJs, ReactJs, HTML, CSS, and SASS) with high consideration for web accessibility.

He is passionate about open-source and also making the web more accessible to everyone, he enjoys writing articles, sharing his knowledge.

EDUCATION

BABCOCK UNIVERSITY, Ilishan-Remo, Nigeria

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science (Technology) 2017 - 2021

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS	PROF	ESSIO	NAL	SKILLS
---------------------	------	--------------	-----	--------

VueJs
 NuxtJs
 Vuex
 ReactJs
 Redux
 NodeJs
 MongoDB
 GraphQL
 Strapi
 Technical Writing
 Test Driven Development

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer | Acumen Digital (Lagos, Nigeria) | October 2020 - present

- Implemented frontend-related tasks using VueJS and NuxtJs based on user requirements from the product team.
- Designed interactive UI mockups based on user requirements.
- Improved performance and accessibility of user websites.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites including testing and debugging of code.
- Built user dashboards for data visualization and information management of user data.

Software Developer Intern | Kamusi Project International / USA | August 2018 - September 2018

- Built UI features for web e-learning platform.
- Collaborated with a diverse team in redesigning company website.

enoch@acumen.com.ng